<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gaika&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://gaikanomer9.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gaika&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 12:26:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gaikanomer9.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#100DaysOfDevOps Update v.1</title>
      <link>https://gaikanomer9.com/posts/devops2-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 12:26:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaikanomer9.com/posts/devops2-100/</guid>
      <description>11 days into the challenge and first results are here. Another Qwiklab quest about Kubernetes is done and a fantastic course about Networking from Pluralsight by Ross Bagurdes is completed. Besides that, I finished 2 books and articles about building reliable systems which I’ll cover later in separate posts.
🏫Qwiklabs quests about Kubernetes (K8S). Qwiklabs offers a variety of quests and labs about K8S. But after completing 2 quests devoted to Kubernetes and Kubernetes in GCP I found myself in a situation where I would type some commands into the Cloud shell inside GCP without really understanding what’s going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#100DaysOfDevOps</title>
      <link>https://gaikanomer9.com/posts/devops1-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 12:26:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaikanomer9.com/posts/devops1-100/</guid>
      <description>DevOps and Cloud continue to be one of the most demanded skills in the IT market. I can see a lot of trending DevOps learning topics in Google Trends/YouTube and other platforms. At the same time amount of available educational resources is a bit overwhelming: online courses, books and special e-learning platforms.
As I decided to renew and deepen my knowledge in DevOps and surrounding topics I started a #100DaysOfDevOps challenge where I will learn, read and pass courses about the required technologies every day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>